{
  "topic_id":"111",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "John's mom ________ him home from school most days.",
      "choice": ["Drived", "Driving", "Drive", "Drives"],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "One day last year John ___________ for his mom at the front door.",
      "choice": ["Will wait", "Wait", "Waited", "Did wait"],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "John's mom ___________ insurance money for the car next month.",
      "choice": ["Collected", "Will collect", "Collect", "Collecting"],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Today tropical plants ______ in the northern forests.",
      "choice": ["Grew", "Grow", "Will grow", "Growing"],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "I ___________ the bell six times but no one opened the door.",
      "choice": ["was ringing", "have rung", "rang", "will ring"],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Choose the correct verb to fill in the blank.\n Mom ___________ the potatoes for dinner.",
      "choice": ["mash", "mashes", "mashing", "none"],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [{ "mash": "መፍጨት" }]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Our team will have been playing together for six months by the time the championships roll around.\n What tense is the sentence written in?",
      "choice": [
        "Simple future",
        "Continuous future",
        "Perfect future",
        "Perfect continuous future"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Our family will be having pizza on Friday night.\n What tense is the sentence written in?",
      "choice": [
        "Simple future",
        "Continuous future",
        "Perfect future",
        "Perfect continuous future"
      ],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "In May, I will have lived here for ten years.\n What tense is the sentence written in?",
      "choice": [
        "Simple future",
        "Continuous future",
        "Perfect future",
        "Perfect continuous future"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "How do you change the verb 'chide' to past tense?",
      "choice": ["add ing", "add ed", "drop the e and add ed", "add an s"],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [{ "chide": "ጩኸት" }]
    }
  ]
}
